<object clone="/obj/properties" owner="jominey">
  <Core:PropertyContainer>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Core:PCProperties>
      <Core:Property property="chat:actorprop">
         ([ "udat:guide":1 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:callback">([  ])</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:cap">100</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:history">
         (\{ "21:47 [Monitor\|System] \\"Santiago says OOCly: \\"Nice\\"\\"", "22:26 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"No worries : )\\"\\"", "23:01 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Just please no witnesses since there are none around ^.^\\"\\"", "23:01 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I keep checking ;) But go ahead, I'm listening.\\"\\"", "23:02 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Or rather reading and paying close attention.\\"\\"", "23:04 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Okay, but that is why I am being careful also to whisper but I figured that could be one of the risks.\\"\\"", "23:06 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"Moving on from there, I do want to go on the record and say that Enzo has and continues to share deep plot information with Gen that does make her complicit in numerous crimes. If we continue forward with the aforementioned plan of bombs and fire, she will be more than complicit.\\"\\"", "23:07 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Is Gen pretty much doomed at this point or already moreso than she already is damned? I am hoping maybe some good may come of being a willing participant of this plot. :)\\"\\"", "23:09 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Yeah, she is pissed off enough at this point by the reaction and how she is being treated. I mean seriously, I think she has about three friends now, one is indeed a VP *points at Enzo* So I understand. I just hope that there is also possibility of something positive also coming out of participating. Though I certainly of course enjoy the relationship that is building between she and Enzo. The church said she can't get laid until she gets married, so I don't know if that might be in the cards perhaps ;)\\"\\"", "23:10 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"And I am not talking about TS--I prefer RP and FTB but usually I leave that part up to the other person, so long as they are an actual adult.\\"\\"", "23:10 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"I can't predict how any of it will play out until we are live, but it has been made very clear you are fraternizing with one of the big guns on the wrong side of the tracks for this overarching plotline and that in and of itself will have consequences, even if we don't continue into the more nitty gritty aspects of actually committing crime\\"\\"", "23:13 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"*nods* Understood. Right now, Gen is just absolutely fuming from that encounter back there so... I don't know how things will play out, and she (and I) were taken aback to learn that he is a -bit- /end sarcasm/ psychotic, yet ironically... that falls into my usual tastes. Rooting for Phantom and Raoul is a tool, etc ;)\\"\\"", "23:14 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"And how she is beating treated in general and Enzo's injuries and how they are talking about him. She may be young and naive but... I get it's a risk.\\"\\"", "23:14 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"He's a serial killer. You healed all his wounds sustained in attempted murders while knowing they were wounds sustained during attempted murders \<.\< lol\\"\\"", "23:15 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol. I did. I really did.\\"\\"", "23:15 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I was going to write him a note saying \\"Next time, push harder.\\" XD\\"\\"", "23:16 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Poor sweet Gen is in love with a psychic serial killer. *sigh* Her parents would be so proud! ;D\\"\\"", "23:16 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"lmfao ok then. so if you are down for actually committing crime, you'll need to @yes to @complicit.\\"\\"", "23:18 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"And while I would prefer not to kill Gen, if we did, I do hope it's at least a good death scene. I just hate losing all the traits with the STPs I put into her. Lol, I have another guy in the closet that Gus is willing to murder on her behalf I have been waiting to pull out too. But I can give him Enzo instead since Gus isn't around ^.^\\"\\"", "23:19 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, so so far, her closest friends are murderers. All three.\\"\\"", "23:19 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Santiago wants to kill Kilana, Gus my NPC French Fop, and Enzo... well, alot of people *grins*\\"\\"", "23:20 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"Nope, no death. But there is a very high probability you'll be scarlet lettered. We only do death with explicit consent. If you're willing to be that person and keep your circle relegated to those of a like mind, you'll get a good story and some street cred out of it.\\"\\"", "23:20 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, she already is!\\"\\"", "23:21 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"And I'm cool with that :) It's certainly a turn for Gen I did NOT expect but the world has been a bit cruel to her and she is turning darker than I ever expected. I am enjoying it!\\"\\"", "23:22 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I do love a good story \<3\\"\\"", "23:23 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"The reward is the story, at its core. The perks alongside that imo pale in comparison to being part of a storyline that is culminating around the five year anniversary mark. It's history making stuff.\\"\\"", "23:25 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I very much appreciate you pulling me in and letting me participate. I've rather enjoyed it so far. Gen is something of a long fuse, but that fuse is about to go and I actually have been working on something for you/Enzo that I do hope you appreciate. I wanted to have it done by Christmas but it's been hard for me to sit at the computer. But I have one particular poem that I wrote with Enzo and her mind as a Doctor specifically. So... I'm working on it and hope to be able to give it to Enzo soon :)\\"\\"", "23:28 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Life has been kicking me in the teeth lately, so I just hope throughout the crazy that some good will come of it. I do actually want Gen to be a Mom at some point. But I sort of want her to be married first ^.^ I'm not saying IT MUST BE ENZO --  I'm just letting you know that is one of my hopes for her\\"\\"", "23:29 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"It's definitely a distinct arc on the villain side, especially if she really is down for burning down a residential structure with a lot of important people in it\\"\\"", "23:29 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"At this point, yes.\\"\\"", "23:29 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Give her a mask or cloak or both, and give her the fucking match.\\"\\"", "23:30 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"She will like the big boom ;)\\"\\"", "23:31 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"marry your dude before you have someone kill him lolol\\"\\"", "23:31 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"That's my hope! Lol!\\"\\"", "23:32 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Aww, love, you will grow up to kill those assholes some day.\\"\\"", "23:36 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"She's pissed off at whomever hurt him.\\"\\"", "00:50 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol\\"\\"", "01:52 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, my lord in Portuguese\\"\\"", "20:52 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Hi hi!\\"\\"", "20:52 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo says OOCly: \\"shit I walked away and so many people showed haha back\\"\\"", "20:53 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, wb!\\"\\"", "20:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Enzo privately messages Valentin: \\"possibly grab or add it to something like pie\\"\\"", "20:58 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Damn!\\"\\"", "20:59 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"So many calories...\\"\\"", "21:05 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I thought I had follow on...\\"\\"", "21:18 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, can I speak safely?\\"\\"", "21:19 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, I think my heart stopped there for a few beats XD\\"\\"", "21:51 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"fool rather\\"\\"", "00:27 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"I was JUST talking with another player about joining up with Peace.\\"\\"", "00:49 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Lol, I see.... The view to the north overlooks the road leading out of the city. Looking through:\\"\\"", "01:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Iggy, misread\\"\\"", "02:29 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Crap, sorry, thought the french was on\\"\\"", "02:31 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Can I put that inside? That is a storypointed item\\"\\"", "02:32 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Phew, kk. :)\\"\\"", "02:43 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"How do I target the bloody things?\\"\\"", "02:43 [Monitor\|System] \\"Genvieve says OOCly: \\"Oh nm, cuffs work\\"\\"", "04:24 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"eek sorry! was distracted\\"\\"", "04:26 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"aw\\"\\"", "04:27 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"cats just hate attention being on anything except them!\\"\\"", "04:39 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"ooo are they pregnant emits?!\\"\\"", "04:39 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"omg love that\\"\\"", "04:41 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"xDD thats fun though - also means less having to remember to act pregnant too much \>_\>\\"\\"", "04:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"\>_\> okay xx\\"\\"", "04:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"ruins!\\"\\"", "04:58 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"ugh i better go do some work\\"\\"", "04:59 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"yup!!! thank you for being around though \<3 its so early for you guys\\"\\"", "05:00 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"you. tooo!!\\"\\"", "05:00 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"ciao xxx\\"\\"", "21:26 [Monitor\|System] \\"Santiago says OOCly: \\"?\\"\\"", "10:55 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"oh man i have to go\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus says OOCly: \\"Byeee\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"im so sorry, i thought i had longer\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\" i miss you!\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus privately messages Milli: \\"Miss you too love\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"message me okay?\\"\\"", "10:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus privately messages Milli: \\"You got it\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"pics as well!! i'll message you whenever i get the chance to play too, things are slowing down so i have more time, its currently 11pm im not sure of time diff now\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli says OOCly: \\"it was good to see you both!! \<3 sorry for running\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"\<3 \<3 \<3\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus privately messages Milli: \\"It's only 9am lol\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"omg thats a big diff\\"\\"", "10:57 [Monitor\|System] \\"Milli privately messages Valdus: \\"okay byeee xxxx\\"\\"", "11:09 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus says OOCly: \\"Fuck now -I- gotta go\\"\\"", "11:09 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus says OOCly: \\"I'm sorrryyy, it was nice meeting you (:\\"\\"", "11:09 [Monitor\|System] \\"Valdus says OOCly: \\"I'll try to be around more lol\\"\\"", "12:43 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"It's alright!\\"\\"", "13:24 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Phone.. I will be slow\\"\\"", "13:34 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Phone's done.. but I'm going to take a little toilet break \>.\>\\"\\"", "01:56 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"It's okay!\\"\\"", "02:29 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"I hope it's in the same spot. want to walk fast or slooow?\\"\\"", "02:30 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Uhh.. I'll go fast!\\"\\"", "02:35 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Your dress is probably 'under' your chemise.\\"\\"", "02:36 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Yup, haha. You should redress :P\\"\\"", "02:37 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"@undress would get you nude, then you can re-layer\\"\\"", "02:44 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Oi. How funny!\\"\\"", "03:35 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"It's getting fairly late for me. Would it be an okay time to fade out?\\"\\"", "03:37 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\":P If I weren't getting over a cold, I'd value my sleep less. But I'm on at these hours fairly often!\\"\\"", "03:38 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"Sorry to get to the fun and then have to slip out :)\\"\\"", "03:41 [Monitor\|System] \\"Khole says OOCly: \\"\<.\< I would lvoe to keep going. But I got to go. \<3\\"\\"", "20:22 [Monitor\|System] \\"Lope says OOCly: \\"I only have a few minutes tho\\"\\"" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-emote">
         "(time) [(chat)] \\"(chatter)"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-end">
         "\\""
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-evoke">
         "(time) [(chat)\|(chatter)] \\""
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:listeners">
         (\{ \<Chatters:AE:to:topsy\>, \<Chatters:AE:ti:tiamat\>, \<Chatters:AE:me:melinoe\> \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:name">"Monitor"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:notips">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:notitle">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:prefer">([  ])</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:purpose">
         "Guide monitoring"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:style">"assist"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name">"Monitor"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1584920788, "jominey", "E", 1584920965, "jominey", "E", 1584921318, "jominey", "E", 1584923733, "jominey", "E", 1595220746, "jominey", "E", 1706074604, "annemairi", "E", 1706074717, "annemairi", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
    </Core:PCProperties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Core:PropertyContainer>
</object>
