<object clone="/base/obj/thing" owner="zwoc">
  <Base:Thing>
    <Ur:UrObject/>
    <Base:Bulk immobile="false" mass="1" density="1"/>
    <Base:Container flexible="false" transparent-container="false" public-container="false" tight="false" capacity="0" maxweight="0"/>
    <Base:Misc gender="neuter" volition="false" weapon="false" default_stance="none" combinable="false" discrete="false" by_weight="false" tight="false" scriptrunner="false">
      <Base:Edible value="false"/>
      <Base:Potable value="false"/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DrinkMessageThird/>
      <Base:Transparency value="false"/>
      <Base:Unsafe value="false"/>
      <Base:Safe value="false"/>
      <Base:ClothesExpected value="false"/>
      <Base:DieMessageFirst/>
      <Base:DieMessageThird/>
    </Base:Misc>
    <Base:Details/>
    <Base:Combat>
      <Base:Strength value="1"/>
      <Base:MaxFatigue value="1"/>
    </Base:Combat>
    <Base:Clothing>
      <Base:SingleWear value="false"/>
    </Base:Clothing>
    <Base:Crafting see_level="0" do_level="0" time="0" attention="false" held="false">
      <Base:Ingredients/>
      <Base:Tools/>
      <Base:CraftVerbs/>
    </Base:Crafting>
    <Base:InitialContents/>
    <Base:InitialProperties/>
    <Core:Properties>
      <Core:Property property="chat:callback">
         ([ \<Chatters:IC:eo:eos\>:50 ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:cap">50</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:history">
         (\{ "16:42 [Plotters\|StoryPlotter Ditto] \\"How long will that take?  If it's not long I'll try to get this room working then we can start the plot\\"", "16:42 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"10 min\\"", "17:01 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"3 destriers are done and statted... may be too hard or may not. I can never tell anymore. Certainly tougher than any one pc, but current combat system doesn't seem to have as much differentiation between mid level and high level. That octopus had foolish stats to last any length of time.\\"", "17:01 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Probably not tough enough as I think about it....\\"", "17:02 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"On the other hand... they've spent a lot of tokens to have fire support... so that is fine\\"", "17:03 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"just going to up their speed a bunch so they don't go too infrequently\\"", "17:04 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Okay. Starting fire right now RL will be back in 10. Doubt destriers will need to show up that fast, if they do.. just grab them from my inventory. The first one is the one I assumed would fall into the pit and thus they don't need to fight. If they start to though, it is their fault.\\"", "17:18 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Hokay\\"", "17:20 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"How things coming?\\"", "17:32 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"I'm possessing it btw\\"", "17:32 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Want to come running right into the pit?\\"", "17:34 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Im listening now. I changed bodies sorry\\"", "17:35 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"So what do you want me to do? Run into the pit?\\"", "17:35 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Yes please. Get frighted when they grab you or come near you and run into the pit\\"", "17:35 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Target it as pit\\"", "17:41 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Sunta is going to break up the group.  I'll need you to run these scene spot.  I'll take them to the other place.\\"", "17:44 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"What do you want me to do?\\"", "17:44 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Make this one cry out and stuff.  Spawn the arm and make one of the other two be gnawing on it when they respond.\\"", "17:45 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Make sure people know the trap is ruined and that the destrier is stuck in the trap\\"", "17:46 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"I didn't have time to code it\\"", "17:49 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"I'm still with yo spot.  I can play one of the drays if you need me too\\"", "17:49 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Why can't I enter fight mode?\\"", "17:50 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"I'm not sure\\"", "18:01 [Plotters\|StoryBuilder Nyx] \\"I made the jewelry assuming it would all have been stolen from graves. If they steal it, could curse it or something\\"", "18:04 [Plotters\|Mack] \\"I didn't know there was jewelry on the body.\\"", "18:05 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"Where is the other one spot?\\"", "18:06 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"I do love him speaking in his own lizard tongue\\"", "18:20 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Did you give yourself the lizard language btw? :P\\"", "18:20 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Or want to have the snipers dealing with the others?\\"", "18:21 [Plotters\|A cool breeze] \\"I need to lay down.  I can't play anymore.  I'm really sorry guys.\\"", "18:24 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"No worries, be healthy\\"", "22:24 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Btw Nyx, who played the graverobber? I let them retrieve his things\\"", "22:24 [Plotters\|StoryBuilder Nyx] \\"Ditto played him, I think. I don't know, I wasn't involved at all outside of building him and some other things.\\"", "22:25 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"I think she forgot some things being so exhausted for hints for PCs. Even the story changed from what was discused.. from them smuggling things out and getting set upon by destriers to the vampires killing them and leaving one as bait for the pcs. Or at least that is the impression Fyros got and passed on.\\"", "22:26 [Plotters\|StoryBuilder Nyx] \\"I don't know. I offered to help play something, but it seemed like you two had it under control. I know Fyros was the one keeping the graverobber alive for a bit and getting info from him, but I've no idea what was said or not said\\"", "22:29 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"I wasn't there and Ditto was pretty out of it at the end, dunno what happened. She bailed partway through though just too exhausted, and obviously no problems with that, but wasn't sure what was said or wasn't.\\"", "23:07 [Plotters\|StoryBuilder Nyx] \\"My husband said people assume it was the vampires because they asked Mack who did that to him and Mack said 'They'. When they asked They who? He laughed bloodily and said 'They' again. He told them that he was smuggling vamps out of the city with dead bodies, so they assume that he got repaid for his acts by being attacked by them\\"", "23:09 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"*nod* I think that must have been Ditto getting tired and not clear. Ah well.\\"", "23:09 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Can't blame her with the chemo\\"", "11:05 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"So.. lets see, I think some of the clues Mack might have given then got skipped because of your being tired. They were left with the impression that the vampires were smuggled out then killed the graverobbers themselves leaving one as a trap for the PC.\\"", "11:06 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"They also attacked the destrier in the pit rather than just leave it there, and it was a brute. Took 3 PCs to near fatal damage, Fyros, Althea and Eiryk. We're consideirng giving each a permanent scar/disfiguring mark at the worst wound  for having gone so far in combat, and a temporary stat penalty/lame gait to show they are recovering from a bad injury.\\"", "11:07 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"They also collected the graverobbed treasures so we need to come up with curses to apply to those who end up with the items.\\"", "11:15 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Overall I suppose it went ok. Fights went off, they know vampires are out of city, they get some cursed items. Not quite how we envisioned.\\"", "11:15 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"I was a bit slow with some things\\"", "11:16 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Lots of folk in the combat and I wanted to let everyone have an effect. Of course they chose to fight the biggest of the destrier rather than leave it.\\"", "11:16 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"A couple folk did try to tame it.. Primarily Nix, just didn't have enough skill to do so.\\"", "02:54 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Test\\"", "02:55 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Test\\"", "02:58 [Plotters\|Spot] \\"Test\\"" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-emote">
         "(time) [(chat)] \\"(chatter)"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-end">
         "\\""
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:layout-evoke">
         "(time) [(chat)\|(chatter)] \\""
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:listeners">
         (\{ \<Chatters:AE:az:azrael\>, \<Chatters:IC:me:mercutio\> \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:name">"Plotters"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:notitle">1</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:prefer">
         ([ "abiwan":"Bast", "arrianna":"Cake", "balkaar":"Sirazad", "barbra18":"Quo", "belle":"Belle", "catharsis":"Leah", "delfina":"Karma", "haystack":"Cade", "kymberlee":"Jersey", "librarysage":"Pan", "missk":"Eos", "morwenlorelie":"Cersei", "numbat":"Katie", "ocannie":"Geli", "pp74":"Eos", "publicenemy":"Eros", "rastalabor":"Spot", "rhenn":"Natalia", "rorschakovacs":"Guinness", "sanc_the_dark":"Burcet", "tangerine":"Aurelius", "thyenehyas":"Banana", "tunk_bodin":"Death" ])
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:purpose">
         "StoryPlotters only"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="chat:style">
         "plotters"
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="name">"Plotters"</Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="revisions">
         (\{ 1060820017, "zwoc", "E", 1060820056, "zwoc", "E", 1061923327, "zwoc", "E", 1061923390, "zwoc", "E", 1061923424, "zwoc", "E", 1061923699, "zwoc", "E", 1062091741, "zwoc", "X", 1535986565, "jominey", "E" \})
      </Core:Property>
      <Core:Property property="skill:fatigue">1.0</Core:Property>
    </Core:Properties>
    <Notes:Notes/>
  </Base:Thing>
</object>
