<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/lognode" owner="SkotOS">
  <Log:LogNode tag="Suspend Log" assignee="unassigned-255">
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8160" stamp="1382340537" date="Oct 21 03:28" head="StoryPlotter Eos[pp74] unsuspended novaaezian's account">
       novaaezian's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8161" stamp="1388876445" date="Jan  4 18:00" head="StoryGoddess Eos[pp74] unsuspended arikon's account">
       arikon's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8162" stamp="1402289650" date="Jun  9 00:54" head="StoryCoder Azrael[tonyd] unsuspended aahzmandius's account">
       aahzmandius's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8163" stamp="1413468425" date="Oct 16 10:07" head="StoryGuide Taran[jominey] suspended tucker102's account">
       tucker102's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Violating TOS by sharing alt information with another player
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8164" stamp="1414978943" date="Nov  2 20:42" head="StoryCoder Roo[jominey] unsuspended tucker102's account">
       tucker102's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8165" stamp="1427916280" date="Apr  1 15:24" head="StoryGuide Taran[jominey] suspended meandmine's account">
       meandmine's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Promoting a rape plot IG and then lying to staff about it
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8166" stamp="1428549142" date="Apr  8 23:12" head="StoryCoder Roo[jominey] unsuspended meandmine's account">
       meandmine's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8167" stamp="1431929975" date="May 18 02:19" head="StoryCoder Azrael[tonyd] suspended rastalabor's account">
       rastalabor's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Multiple complaints of harassment and pressuring of other players.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8168" stamp="1459199961" date="Mar 28 17:19" head="StoryCipher Roo[jominey] suspended bethor's account">
       bethor's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Making players feel uncomfortable with @ooc conversations and making assumptions about alts. He's been warned about this behavior and continued to do it after promising to stop.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8169" stamp="1459807323" date="Apr  4 18:02" head="StoryCipher Roo[jominey] unsuspended bethor's account">
       bethor's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8170" stamp="1459921894" date="Apr  6 01:51" head="StoryHost Azrael[tonyd] suspended heavenlyheather's account">
       heavenlyheather's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Suspended for lying. Unban on Apr 14 please
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8171" stamp="1459921903" date="Apr  6 01:51" head="StoryHost Azrael[tonyd] suspended fangbanger's account">
       fangbanger's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Suspended for lying. Unban on Apr 14 please
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8172" stamp="1460525427" date="Apr 13 01:30" head="StoryHost Azrael[tonyd] unsuspended fangbanger's account">
       fangbanger's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8173" stamp="1460525431" date="Apr 13 01:30" head="StoryHost Azrael[tonyd] unsuspended heavenlyheather's account">
       heavenlyheather's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8174" stamp="1469929548" date="Jul 30 21:45" head="StoryBuilder Topsy[ezralee] suspended shentino's account">
       shentino's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Third and final warning about keeping his alts separated from one another as much as possible.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8175" stamp="1470274844" date="Aug  3 21:40" head="StoryBuilder Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended shentino's account">
       shentino's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8176" stamp="1520213180" date="Mar  4 20:26" head="StoryEnforcer Dozier[lidiab] suspended olmsteadl's account">
       olmsteadl's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Disregarding warnings of harrassment
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8177" stamp="1520213215" date="Mar  4 20:26" head="StoryEnforcer Dozier[lidiab] suspended seraphilomena's account">
       seraphilomena's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given:  Disregarding warnings of harrassment
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8178" stamp="1521419129" date="Mar 18 20:25" head="StoryBuilder Cosmo[lidiab] unsuspended seraphilomena's account">
       seraphilomena's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8179" stamp="1521419232" date="Mar 18 20:27" head="StoryBuilder Cosmo[lidiab] unsuspended olmsteadl's account">
       olmsteadl's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8180" stamp="1522892189" date="Apr  4 21:36" head="StoryBuilder Topsy[ezralee] suspended seraphilomena's account">
       seraphilomena's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: PERMANENT BAN for reasons of stalking, harassment, TOS violations, alt abuse and player manipulation.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8181" stamp="1522892215" date="Apr  4 21:36" head="StoryBuilder Topsy[ezralee] suspended olmsteadl's account">
       olmsteadl's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: PERMANENT BAN for reasons of stalking, harassment, TOS violations, alt abuse and player manipulation.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8182" stamp="1545279332" date="Dec 19 23:15" head="StoryGuide Athos[reivns] suspended shentino's account">
       shentino's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: 72 hr suspension for abusing staff verbally.  Account being reviewed for permanent ban.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8183" stamp="1586123758" date="Apr  5 17:55" head="StoryHost Roo[jominey] suspended chindora's account">
       chindora's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Let me start by saying this will not be an easy conversation to have. Word of your unhappiness with staff and the game has reached us more times than I can count and we are stonewalled every time we try to start an open dialogue with you about these problems. Players and staff alike have reached out to us talking of the toxicity that surrounds the OOC comments you make. You often lie and/or exaggerate staff stances on certain topics in what can only be seen as an attempt to undermine our authority. We understand that a number of players trust you and the fact you use that trust to tell misinformation or defame staff is not something we will tolerate any further. When multiple players, including the majority of staff, are ready to walk because of a single person, drastic action needs to be taken. Due to the violations of ToS that have been reported, and that we have observed (sections 6.c and 6.j), we have made the decision to suspend your account from our game indefinitely. As we typically do in these situations, we will refund any storypoint purchases you have made in the last year. This is not an invitation for a discussion; we have tried that already. This is merely a notice of a final decision.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8184" stamp="1586867665" date="Apr 14 08:34" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended gooberg99's account">
       gooberg99's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Suspended for 6 mo minumum for breaking the zero-tolerance rule about trigger warning topics. Please see !staff for more details.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8185" stamp="1607993948" date="Dec 14 19:59" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended shentino's account">
       shentino's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8186" stamp="1616379798" date="Mar 21 22:23" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended flaeib's account">
       flaeib's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: [OOC Page] accepted by Baronet Matteo: "[Mar 21 11:04] On Feb 24, we had a discussion in which you were given an official warning about the aggressive and abusive way in which you handle stressful situations and communicate with players. Yesterday, I was contacted by a number of players who provided logs of the incident in the post office and we have decided that this situation was in breech of the warning you received about your tone and behavior. In addition to this, we have also been alerted to your repeated usage of OOC channels to coerce players into sexual scenes IC. This is also a pattern of behavior that you have been repeatedly warned about. As such, we have made the decision to impose a two week suspension on your account, effective immediately upon receipt of this communication. Upon your return, you will be on a probationary last-chance for an indeterminate period of time. Should you again cross the line, we will be forced to impose stricter consequences. You are welcome to email me at topsy@allegoryofempires.com with any questions or concerns, but this consequence is not up for negotiation.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8187" stamp="1617652656" date="Apr  5 15:57" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended flaeib's account">
       flaeib's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8188" stamp="1618195302" date="Apr 11 22:41" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended cinnamongirl's account">
       cinnamongirl's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: [OOC Page] to [Cinnamongirl/Margratte]: "Rules are rules and all players must follow them. I've given you enough warnings and you continue, so I am going to ask you to leave the scene now. Because of your attitude, tone, and your refusal to adhere to the policies explicitly outlined for you, we will be issuing a two week suspension of this account. Upon lifting of the suspension, you are welcome to return but not as Margrat. Should you continue to refuse to follow the rules, the consequences will be harsher.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8189" stamp="1620422233" date="May  7 17:17" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended cinnamongirl's account">
       cinnamongirl's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8190" stamp="1622672177" date="Jun  2 18:16" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended darkspun's account">
       darkspun's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: [OOC Page] accepted by Arelio: "[Jun  2 17:29] Given your repeated issues with alt abuse and the recent attempt to transfer funds from Sheamus to Arelio, we are imposing a two-week suspension on your account upon receipt of this message. Please note that this is your absolute final warning and should you engage in alt abuse again, your account will be permanently banned. If you have any questions, you are welcome to email me at topsy@allegoryofempires.com
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-255" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8191" stamp="1623906963" date="Jun 17 01:16" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended darkspun's account">
       darkspun's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
  </Log:LogNode>
</object>
