<object clone="/usr/SkotOS/obj/lognode" owner="SkotOS">
  <Log:LogNode tag="Suspend Log" assignee="unassigned-256">
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8192" stamp="1633277939" date="Oct  3 12:18" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended flaeib's account">
       flaeib's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: [OOC Page] accepted by Baronet Matteo: "[Oct  1 15:17] The last time we spoke, you were given the notice that you were on a last-chance probationary period. Since then, we have received numerous reports from multiple players about the following issues: revealing alts, using OOC methods to get sex from players and characters IC, and harassment. All of these are issues you have been warned repeatedly about. Because of this, effective immediately, you are indefinitely banned from Allegory of Empires.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8193" stamp="1633280501" date="Oct  3 13:01" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended flaeib1's account">
       flaeib1's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: [OOC Page] accepted by Baronet Matteo: "[Oct  1 15:17] The last time we spoke, you were given the notice that you were on a last-chance probationary period. Since then, we have received numerous reports from multiple players about the following issues: revealing alts, using OOC methods to get sex from players and characters IC, and harassment. All of these are issues you have been warned repeatedly about. Because of this, effective immediately, you are indefinitely banned from Allegory of Empires.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8194" stamp="1645389441" date="Feb 20 15:37" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended ingen's account">
       ingen's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: For being a pathetic manbaby and making us suffer his ridiculous temper tantrums.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8195" stamp="1646058345" date="Feb 28 09:25" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended adios's account">
       adios's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Suspended on the grounds that you're being a dickhead
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8196" stamp="1646058374" date="Feb 28 09:26" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended weas's account">
       weas's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: please find something better to do with your time, asshat
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8197" stamp="1647490501" date="Mar 17 00:15" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended arikon's account">
       arikon's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: Temporary suspension until a final decision is made regarding OOC crossover.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8198" stamp="1647528046" date="Mar 17 10:40" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended arikon's account">
       arikon's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8199" stamp="1647528093" date="Mar 17 10:41" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended arikon's account">
       arikon's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: After looking through your record of warnings and suspensions over the course of your time with IcO and AoE, we have made the decision to levy a two-week suspension on your account effective 17 March 2022 and ending 31 March 2022. Please be aware that this is your final warning about your problematic behavior. Should we be forced to intervene in the future over any incident of any kind, the consequences for this will be permanent. I encourage you to think carefully about the choices you make moving forward.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8200" stamp="1647743344" date="Mar 19 22:29" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended darkspun's account">
       darkspun's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: As per the ToS and the long-standing rules of both IcO and AoE, revealing the current or former staff identity of PC characters is something we have a zero tolerance policy on. This combined with your consistent patterns of alt abuse, toxic negativity, conspiracy theories, and the frequency with which you disparage your fellow community members past and present has resulted in a pattern of behavior we will no longer tolerate or welcome here. As is standard procedure, I will prorate and refund your PayPal account for the remaining time you have paid. This indefinite banning of your account is effective immediately. I counsel you take the time to reflect on your behavior moving forward wherever you might end up.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8201" stamp="1648729982" date="Mar 31 08:33" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended arikon's account">
       arikon's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8202" stamp="1706649352" date="Jan 30 16:15" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] suspended stacy's account">
       stacy's account has been suspended for this game.

Reason given: It has recently come to our attention that your efforts to ?pull in more people? were done with egregious disregard for basic consent and without any respect for the well-established rules surrounding how OOC information is handled IC. As such, effective immediately, all mentions of Santiago, Giada, and Kilana as pertains to Genvieve are to be completely erased. Furthermore, we ask that you please avoid Kilana?s character and immediately cease all references to the alleged assault by Kilana upon Genvieve. In lieu of this behavior, we are implementing a three week suspension on your account that will commence immediately upon the conclusion of this conversation.
    </Log:Entry>
    <Log:Entry assignee="unassigned-256" tag="Suspend Log" ix="8203" stamp="1708482691" date="Feb 20 21:31" head="StoryHostess Topsy[ezralee] unsuspended stacy's account">
       stacy's account is no longer suspended for this game.
    </Log:Entry>
  </Log:LogNode>
</object>
